export const quiz = [
        {question: "What famous food is Chicago known for?",
        choices: ["Grapes", "Noodles", "Deep dish pizza"],
        correctAnswer: "Deep dish pizza"},
  {question: "What famous Chicago street is known for its shopping and dining?",
  choices: ["The Magnificent Mile", "Maxwell Street", "Michigan Avenue"],
  correctAnswer: "The Magnificent Mile"},
  {question: "What famous zoo is located in Chicago?", 
  choices: ["Denver Zoo", "Bronx Zoo", "Lincoln Park Zoo"],
  correctAnswer: "Lincoln Park Zoo"},
  {question: "Chicago, Illinois is located at the south end of which of the five US Great Lakes?",
  choices: ["Lake Superior", "Lake Michigan", "Great Bear Lake"],
  correctAnswer: "Lake Michigan"},
  {question: "Where in Chicago is the University of Chicago's main campus?",
  choices: ["Chinatown", "Englewood", "Hyde Park"],
  correctAnswer: "Hyde Park"},
  {question: "How many stars are on the official Chicago flag?",
  choices: ["3", "4", "5"],
  correctAnswer: "4"},
  {question: "What does Chicago's motto, \"Urbs in Horto\", mean?",
  choices: ["Windy City", "Grassy Town", "City In A Garden"],
  correctAnswer: "City In A Garden"},
  {question: "Where in Chicago is the Adler Planetarium located?",
  choices: ["Logan Square", "Northerly Island", "Lincoln Park"],
  correctAnswer: "Northerly Island"},
  {question: "What is the three-letter code for Chicago O'Hare International Airport?",
  choices: ["PIT", "HRL", "ORD"],
  correctAnswer: "ORD"},
  {question: "What is an outdoor amphitheater located on the man-made peninsula of Northerly Island?",
  choices: ["Huntington Bank Pavilion", "Black Rock", "East River Pavilion"],
  correctAnswer: "Huntington Bank Pavilion"},
  {question: "Which hotel was named for the Chicago and Northwestern Railroad Vice President?",
  choices: ["Hilton", "Howard Johnson", "Alex Johnson"],
  correctAnswer: "Alex Johnson"},
  {question: "What famous building is located at 210 South Canal Street in Chicago?",
  choices: ["The Rookery", "Pittsfield Building", "The Union Station"],
  correctAnswer: "The Union Station"},
  {question: "The city of Chicago is often referred to by what nickname?",
  choices: ["Beantown", "The Windy City", "The Loop"],
  correctAnswer: "The Windy City"},
  {question: "What is the stadium the Chicago Bears play home games?",
  choices: ["Wrigley Field", "Soldier Field", "Toyota Park"],
  correctAnswer: "Wrigley Field"},
  {question: "Chicago Midway International Airport uses which airport code?",
  choices: ["SUX", "TXK", "MDW"],
  correctAnswer: "MDW"},
  {question: "Who built the first settlement on the land that is now Chicago in 1779?",
  choices: ["Jean George", "Jean Baptist Point Dusable", "Art Modell"],
  correctAnswer: "Jean Baptist Point Dusable"},
  {question: "What is the tallest building in Chicago?",
  choices: ["Trump International", "John Hancock Center", "Willis Tower"],
  correctAnswer: "Willis Tower"},
  {question: "What hotel is located at the northern end of Michigan Avenue in Chicago?",
  choices: ["Drake Hotel", "MGM Grand", "The Grand Hotel"],
  correctAnswer: "Drake Hotel"},
  {question: "What is the world's largest food festival, held annually in mid-July in Chicago?",
  choices: ["Bite Of Chicago", "Taste Of Chicago", "Dish Of Chicago"],
  correctAnswer: "Taste Of Chicago"},
  {question: "One of the most famous landmarks in Chicago, this fabled structure survived the Great Fire.",
  choices: ["The Chicago Water Tower", "Wrigley Field", "Field Museum"],
  correctAnswer: "The Chicago Water Tower"}
    ];

    

 




  